

HARD SKILLS

HTML, CSS **SCSS** JavaScript npm, Gulp Git Photoshop, Figma Visual Studio Code

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate (B1)

Russian

SOFT SKILLS

Analytical thinking

Teamwork

Adaptive

Ability to learn

Great performance

Interpersonal skills

Viktoria Enokyan

Frontend developer

vika-yenokyan@mail.ru

github.com/VikaYenokyan

+7(929) 009-21-58

@vi_ku_lik

Voronezh, Russia

Master's student at Voronezh State University. I had practical experience in using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, npm, GULP, SCSS, PHP, CMS 1C-Bitrix. Completed an internship under the guidance of experienced mentor. Worked as a 1C programmer at the First Bit company, then worked as a web programmer

EXPERIENCE

Frontend developer intern

February, 2022 June, 2022

Angels IT I Voronezh

Create of a library of design system components

Frontend developer intern

July, 2022 August, 2022

Neoflex I Voronezh

Create a web application using the API

1C programmer

May, 2023 October, 2023

First Bit I Voronezh

Installation, configuration and training in working with 1C programs

Web-programmer

November, 2023 April, 2024

First Bit I Voronezh

Work in the Internet projects department: layout of sites and individual elements; work with hosting; updating PHP versions; working with CMS Bitrix, Drupal, Wordpress; improvement of website functionality on CMS Bitrix; template customization.

EDUCATION

Faculty of Applied Mathematics, Informatics and mechanics,

Voronezh State University

Voronezh State University

2021 - 2023

Master

Faculty of Applied Mathematics, Informatics and mechanics.

Bachelor

2017 - 2021

Udemy

Course "Full Course in JavaScript

Udemy

+ React"

PROJECTS

Course "Web Developer

https://vikayenokyan.github.io/

https://get8.1bitvrn36.ru/